http://www.jta.org/privacy-policy

Search ToggleSearch toggle
Search for:
Privacy Policy
Last Revised: March 1, 2017
This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains what information the JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY (“JTA” or “we” “our” or “us”) collects on our Websites (the “Websites”), how we use your information, and your choices. This Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices and sets out your obligations and ours with respect to your use of the Websites. This Privacy Policy only covers information collected on our Websites, and does not cover any information collected by any other websites or offline by JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY (unless specifically stated) or any other company. By visiting the Websites, you agree to abide by the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.
This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time in order to address new issues and to reflect changes on the Websites or in the law. We reserve the right to revise or make any changes to this Privacy Policy, and your continual use of the Websites subsequent to any changes to this Privacy Policy will mean that you accept such changes. You can tell that this Privacy Policy has been updated by checking the last revised date posted on the top of this page. If due to such changes, you decide that you want to remove any portion of your personal information from our database, please contact us at webmaster@70facesmedia.org. If the policy is revised substantially, affected registrants or subscribers may receive an e-mail outlining the change.
BY VISITING THE WEBSITES, YOU CONSENT TO OUR USING ANY INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US OR THAT WE COLLECT, IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF USE, DO NOT VISIT OR USE THE WEBSITES.
Information JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY Collects
In order to access certain portions of the Websites, or if you choose to participate in certain features, such as registering to become a member of JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY, receiving one of our newsletters, ordering publications or making a donation, you may need to register and provide certain personally identifiable information (“PII”) about yourself, such as but not limited to your name, address, e-mail address, phone number or credit card information. In addition, we may on occasion provide you the opportunity to provide PII, such as name or e-mail address, of someone else, such as if you choose to e-mail a friend an article or make a donation in the name of someone else.
To enable donations via the JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY Websites, we collect and store name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card information and other billing information. This information will only be shared with third parties who help to complete the purchase transaction. Examples of this include fulfilling orders and processing credit card payments.
In addition, when you visit our Websites, our web servers automatically collect certain non-PII, such as the number and frequency of visitors to our web pages and the length of their stays, browser type, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting our Websites, and IP addresses (see below for more information on IP addresses). We also may determine the technology available through your browser in order to serve you the most appropriate version of a web page.
For people who choose to become registered members of JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY, upon completion of the registration process, we will send you a validation e-mail message.
For subscribers to JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY’s free e-newsletters, JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY uses a double opt-in process. After you provide your name and e-mail address via our Websites, you will also need to reply to a validation e-mail to fully activate your subscription.
By signing up for a JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY e-newsletter, you agree to receive E-mail Offers sent to you by JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY on behalf of sponsors of JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY. JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY will provide clear ways to stop receiving these e-mails in each e-mail offer it sends. At no time will any PII you have provided JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY be disclosed to any third party for the purposes of transmitting E-mail offers to you, though we may share information about our readership in aggregate with third parties.
Additionally, if you contact us, we may keep a record of your correspondence, including any information or PII contained therein.
You may decline to provide any personal information, but please realize that you thereby may be unable to register for, or participate in, certain of our services.
JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY does not rent, sell, barter or give away its user or member lists or its users’ or members’ names, e-mail addresses or mailing addresses for use by sponsors and other third parties for the purpose of solicitations, unless the user has previously given his or her consent.
JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY Does Not Knowingly Collect Information From Children Under Thirteen Years Of Age.
This is not a Websites directed to children under the age of 13, and JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY does not knowingly collect any PII from children under thirteen years of age. If you are under thirteen years of age, do not send any information about yourself to JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY. If JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY with PII, JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY will delete that child’s PII from its system.
JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY recommends parental supervision when a child uses the Internet, particularly when a child enters a forum or uses e-mail. We also encourage parents to instruct their children not to give out personal information in these areas.
Use Of IP Addresses
An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer or network when you are on the Internet. When you request pages from this Websites, our servers log your IP address. JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY may use IP addresses for a number of purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to audit the use of the Websites.
Cookies
Like most Websites, our Websites may sometimes make use of browser “cookies.” Cookies are pieces of information that websites either transfer to your computer’s hard drive or stores temporarily in your computer’s memory for record-keeping purposes (also known as session cookies). JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY does not save PII in cookies.
JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY primarily utilizes cookies to understand how many of our visitors are repeat visitors or new users and to exclude to the extent possible users from participating more than once in a survey or poll on our Websites. We may also use cookies to remember your password or otherwise to expedite your logging in to our Websites.
Sponsors may elect to use advertising companies to serve their ads on JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY and JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY publications, and sponsors themselves may also place a cookie on a user’s computer. We do not have access to the cookies or their contents that are placed by sponsors or by third-party advertising companies.
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you choose to disable cookies, you may not be able to fully access and take advantage of some features on our Websites.
JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY’s Use and Disclosure of Collected Information
JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY may use the PII we collect from you and that you provide to us for our and our affiliates’ business purposes and the purpose for which you provided it, including, without limitation, to provide you with the information or content you have requested, to contact you regarding JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY and our products, services and information, or for other purposes disclosed at the time of collection. For instance, we may send you a requested newsletter, or we may contact you for feedback on such newsletters or with regard to making a donation. We may also contact you regarding any problems or questions we have relating to your use of our Websites, or, in our discretion, to notify you of changes to our Privacy Policy or other policy or terms that affect you and your use of our Websites. We may also use information about our users, including PII, for internal purposes.
If you e-mail someone else an article or otherwise provide someone else’s PII, we will use the information you provide about someone else to send that person the requested e-mail or otherwise fulfill your request, but we will not use the PII you supply us for those activities to send you or your friend any other communications unless otherwise disclosed at the time you provide such information.
JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on its behalf. Examples include, without limitation, hosting our Websites, processing credit card transactions, sending communications on our behalf, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service. These third parties may have access to our Websites’ user information, including PII, but only to the extent it is needed to perform their duties and functions. Although we seek to limit third-party use of PII, we are not responsible for such third-party use of PII that is not in compliance with this Privacy Policy.
JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY may disclose information about its users, including PII, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, or to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Websites and applicable laws. JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY may also disclose such user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with our rights or property or the rights or property of anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. In addition, JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY may disclose user information, including PII, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all of its assets, or other fundamental corporate change.
JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY may disclose anonymous, aggregated user statistics for a variety of purposes, including describing JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY’s services to prospective partners and other third parties.
Other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we will not contact you with marketing material or share your PII with outside parties unless such use or disclosure is clearly identified at the time you provide your PII or we provide you the opportunity to consent or prohibit such use or disclosure.
Your Choices
If you register for membership on JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY or to receive one of our newsletters, you can notify us if at a later time you decide you no longer wish to be registered or receive the newsletter. If you receive the newsletter via e-mail, follow the instructions on how to unsubscribe at the bottom of each e-mail. You can also ask to be removed from any registration or newsletter subscription by e-mailing webmaster@70facesmedia.org.  If you receive the newsletter on your mobile device, please visit our Websites and follow the instructions for unsubscribing.
In general, a registered member may update or delete the information he or she previously provided to us. At present, that updating should be done via an e-mail to webmaster@70facesmedia.org.
If you choose to delete your membership, all but a transactional record of your membership account will be removed from our databases, though some records may remain on back-up media. Note that by deleting your account, you will cancel your membership and no longer be able to access some aspects of our Websites.
You may also choose to post content to our Websites. You should be aware that any content posted by you to the Websites may be read, collected or used by other Websites visitors. JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY is not responsible for the third-party use of any information, including PII you provide in such manner. By participating in the use of the Websites, you consent to our use or disclosure of any content that you submit.
Information you provide to JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY may be stored by us for an indefinite time. This information includes the registration data as well as information provided in conjunction with various membership services, contests or features available on our Websites.
Security
JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY uses commercially reasonable efforts to secure your PII on JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY’s systems, including limiting access to the PII contained on our servers. If credit card information is transmitted, JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY uses encryption methods, including industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. However, please be aware that unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and therefore, JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY and you do so at your own risk.
Links
Please be aware that our Websites, or information you receive from us via e-mail or on your mobile device, may contain links to other websites and/or online materials that are beyond JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY’s control. If you “click” on the link to such a third party, the “click” takes you outside JEWISH TELEGRAPHIC AGENCY’s service to a websites or other service controlled by the third party or third parties. These third parties may set their own cookies, collect data, solicit PII and/or have their own privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only covers information collected on our Websites, and we encourage you to review the privacy policy of any other website you visit.
Consent to Transfer
Our Websites are operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Websites, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.
Contact Us
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us through webmaster@70facesmedia.org.
